https://www.nswc.ca/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomeYour privacy is critically important to us. At North Shore Winter Club (NSWC), we have a few fundamental principles:We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the ongoing operation of one of our services.Below is our privacy policy, which incorporates these goals.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, NSWC collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. NSWC’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how NSWC’s visitors use its website.NSWC also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. NSWC only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to NSWC’s website choose to interact with NSWC in ways that require NSWC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that NSWC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, if you sign up for an account at this website you will be asked to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with NSWC are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, NSWC collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with NSWC. NSWC does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsNSWC may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. NSWC may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, NSWC does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationNSWC discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on NSWC’s behalf or to provide services available at NSWC’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using NSWC’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. NSWC will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, NSWC discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when NSWC believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of NSWC, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an NSWC website and have supplied your email address, NSWC may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with NSWC and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. NSWC takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. NSWC uses cookies to help NSWC identify and track visitors, their usage of NSWC website, and their website access preferences. NSWC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using NSWC’s website, with the drawback that certain features of NSWC’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf NSWC, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that NSWC goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of NSWC may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.AdsThird party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website or other websites.Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings.CommentsComments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives or missed spam, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives and missed spam.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, NSWC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in NSWC’s sole discretion. NSWC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. © 2020 NSWC Public – Family Athletic Club, North Vancouver | Privacy Policy Site by Glacier Media Digital
X Watch The Game With Our New Livestream Watch Now
